http://www.themeparks-uk.com/privacy

UK Theme Park News | UK Theme Park Offers | UK Theme Park Tickets | UK Theme Park Breaks
Privacy Policy
ThemeParks-UK (www.themeparks-uk.com) ("we", "us" or "our" for short) are registered to collect and process personal data under the Data Protection Act 1998 (the "Act" for short). ThemeParks-UK are data controllers of your personal information for the purposes of the Act.
We respect and safeguard the privacy of the users of ThemeParks-UK ("the website"). This Privacy Policy outlines how we will do this, how we will collect and use your personal information (such as your name, country of origin, date of birth, your email address, mobile telephone number or other contact details) and how you can limit our use of this. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully which should be read together with our website terms and conditions.
What information do we gather?Information is gathered in two ways: (1) indirectly (for example, through our website's technology); and (2) directly (for example, when you provide information on various pages of the website.One example of information we collect indirectly is through Internet access logs. When you access the website, your numeric internet address is automatically collected and is placed in our Internet access logs.We collect information directly from you in a number of ways, one of which is through the use of cookies. We use cookies to remember you when you visit this website to keep track of your browsing patterns and to build up a profile of how you and other users use the website. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to the web browser, which enable the web server to collect information from the browser. Find out more about the use of cookies on http://www.cookiecentral.com.Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser. However, switching off cookies may restrict your use of the website and/or delay or affect the way in which the website operates.We also collect information when you voluntarily submit it to us. On our website, we provide you with the opportunity to register for various services, register for email newsletters, enter promotions and competitions, complete puzzles, purchase products and participate in online surveys. When we collect your information in this way, we will notify you as to how this information will be used. We will also provide you with the opportunity to indicate your preferences as to the use of your information.
Third party advertising cookiesMost of the advertisements you see on the website are generated by third parties. Some of these third parties generate their own cookies to track how many people have seen a particular advertisement (or use the services of third parties to do this), and to track how many people have seen it more than once. These cookies cannot be used to identify an individual; they can only be used for statistical purposes, for example, in providing you with advertisements that are more relevant to your interests. Some of the information gleaned from third party cookies will be aggregated with other anonymous information for statistical purposes. The third party companies that generate these cookies have their own, very strict, privacy policies but we don't have access to these cookies; other than allowing them to be served, we have no role to play in these cookies at all (although we may use statistical information arising from these third party cookies and provided to us by third parties, to improve the targeting of advertisements to users of the website).
Google Analytics__utma, __utmb, __utmc, __utmv, __utmz A random unique number or string of letters and numbers to identify your browser, the times and dates that you interacted with the site recently and the marketing materials or referring pages that led you to the site. Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”), to help us see how our website is used. In doing so information about your use of our website, including your IP address, may be transmitted to Google and stored on servers in the United States. The data collected by Google Analytics is used to analyse how frequently the same people revisit the University website, how the website is found (from advertising or referring websites), and which pages are most frequently viewed. This information is combined with data from thousands of other users to create an overall picture of website use, and is never identified individually or personally and is not linked to any other information we store about you. The longest lasting cookie expires 2 years after your last visit to the website. Others are deleted 6 months, 30 minutes and the moment you close your browser.
Google MapsSID, SAPISID, APISID, SSID, HSID, NID, PREF Various unique identifiers, except for PREF which stores your options such as preferred zoom level. Google set a number of cookies on any page that includes a Google Map. While we have no control over the cookies set by Google, they appear to include a mixture of pieces of information to measure the number and behaviour of Google Maps users. Most of the cookies expire 10 years after your last visit to a page containing a Google Map.
Disqus__utma, __utmb, __utmc, __utmv, __utmz, __qca, disqus_unique, UIDR, mc, UID, testCookie Unique numbers that identify your browser and interaction history, and a unique ID that identifies our service. Disqus set a number of cookies on any page that includes a Disqus comment box. While we have no control over the cookies set by Disqus, they appear to include a mixture of pieces of information to measure the number and behaviour of Disqus users, including information that links your visits to our website with your Google, Facebook, Twitter or Disqus account if you are signed in to one. This cookie does not identify you personally unless you are logged into Disqus, in which case it is linked to your Disqus, Google, Twitter and Facebook accounts. The __utma, -b, -c, -v and –z cookies have the same expiration as our Google Analytics cookies. __qca expires 26 years after your last visit to a page containing Disqus, while disqus unique expires in 6 months.
Javascript checkhas_js A binary value of 1 (true) or 0 (false). This cookie helps the website understand if the browser javascript functionality is enabled or not, so as to proceed accordingly. The cookie is deleted when you close your web browser.
You can visit the trade body representing the advertising bodies for more information on how to opt out of these cookies:
http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp
Use of your informationWe invest in high-quality security and do our utmost to protect user privacy. No data transmission over the Internet can be entirely secure, and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information and/or use of the website. Any information that you send is at your own risk and may be read by others. However once we have received your personal information we use strict procedures to protect the security of your personal information.Any personal information gathered by or supplied to us via the website will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy, in accordance with your wishes as indicated to us and in accordance with the Act.We may use your personal information to:
contact you by mail or telephone to let you know about any of our products, services or promotions (which, in some cases may be provided by third parties) which may be of interest to you unless you have asked us not to. Where we contact you about these items by email, text message, or similar electronic means we will only do this with your permission
ensure materials on the website are presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer.
improve the website and to monitor website usage.
Disclosing your informationWe may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in good-faith believing such action is necessary to comply with the law. We will not sell or otherwise share your personal information with third parties without your consent except in the following instances:
where you have agreed to be contacted by us, we may pass your personal information to third parties who provide various products and services on our behalf.
unless required by applicable law or if we are ordered to do so by a court or other similar body;
as we may think necessary to protect our legal rights, a registered user or third party, or to prevent personal injury;
and/or where we are approached by a potential buyer of our business and/or assets or in relation to any joint venture or other business arrangement. In such circumstances we will be able to pass on your personal information to such third party's advisors and to any prospective buyer, as well as to any other relevant parties.
Accessing and updating your personal informationYou have the right to access the personal information held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information we hold about you, please send an email to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.How do I change my personal details?We want to ensure that we provide you with the best possible service. Please therefore always keep us updated of any changes to your personal information, for example, if your email address changes. You can do this by accessing your account pages on the website or by emailing This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.Where we store your personal informationThe personal information that we collect from you may be sent and stored outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). By registering on the website or sending us your personal information by other means, you are indicating your consent for your personal information to be sent and stored outside the EEA.What does providing us with this information mean?By giving us personal information about you, you agree that your personal information can be used as set out in this Privacy Policy. If we change the Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on this page. Please check the website regularly for any changes to this Privacy Policy.If you don't feel we're adhering to this Privacy Policy, what should you do?If at any time you believe that we have not adhered to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please notify us by email at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. and we will make any efforts we can to determine and solve the problem promptly.Last Updated ( Wednesday, 18 August 2018 )
back to top
UK Theme Park News | UK Theme Park OffersUK Theme Park Tickets | UK Theme Park Breaks
ThemeParks-UK
AboutNewsletterContactTermsPrivacyLinksGuide to Halloween at UK Theme Parks 2020
News, Offers, Tickets & Breaks
UK Theme Park NewsUK Theme Park OffersUK Theme Park TicketsUK Theme Park BreaksUK Theme Park Awards
The Top 10 Countdowns
The Top 10 Theme Parks in the UKThe Top 10 Roller Coasters in the UKThe Top 10 Theme Parks for FamiliesThe Top 10 Theme Parks for ThrillsThe Top 10 Theme Parks in BritainThe Top 10 Best UK Theme Parks
Top
